<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<android.support.v4.widget.NestedScrollView
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android">
<LinearLayout
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:paddingBottom="@dimen/activity_vertical_margin"
    android:paddingLeft="@dimen/activity_horizontal_margin"
    android:paddingRight="@dimen/activity_horizontal_margin"
    android:paddingTop="@dimen/activity_vertical_margin">


    <TextView
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:text="We are a group of crazy people wanting to spread happiness by creating foodgasm all over. We operate from the heart of snacks and sweets- Indore; unbound by the geographical location our team makes the best of food available at your doorstep.\n\nEat up, folks. This phase won't last forever, so you might as well make the best out of it.\n\nYes! Living in the food capital of central India and yes obviously The heart of snacks and sweets, people don't eat to live, instead they LIVE TO EAT. Whenever you read any blog or article about Indore, you would surely find food. And with food comes the love, which every Indori wishes to shower up the most. Visit on any random day to the railway station or airport and open any stranger's bag (obviously with permission), you would surely find out a packet or more, puffed with SEV-MIXTURE.\n\nIt's pretty obvious even, because everybody loves to gift close ones something from the place they visited and keep the speciality of that place with themselves. And Indore being famous for food and spicy combinations of flavours, the best thing this city offers is (Drum Rolls) NAMKEEN, the mouth watering INDORI NAMKEEN. But as soon as you begin to list down the people whom you wish to gift, it starts to extend on and on. Thus the idea came up, why not to drop down all the nankeens to the city itself, leaving upon the tension for quality, quantity and taste to us and travel hassle-free.\n\nWith that idea we planned and made it as a proper model, and shared our vision and ideas with the taste magicians, the manufacturers. And viola they were even more excited than us. That filled us with even more energy to get it done.\n\nSo what's stopping you help yourself from spreading foodgasm, Get set Go!!!\n\nIt was nice conversing with you, we do look forward to fill your plates may it be while accompanying your breakfast or lunch to being idle chakna with liquor ;) because we do love you as a fat kid does to cakes."/>
</LinearLayout>
</android.support.v4.widget.NestedScrollView>